# **Eric Posas**

### Digital Developer (Javascript)

Dallas, TX - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Eric-Posas/b3998b418444cf2d

Hello, I'm Eric Posas, animator and developer. I have been writing code for games, advertising, and web for over 5 years now. Currently exploring backend technology and have a highly adaptable learning style. Currently working in the ad industry, mainly utilizing Javascript and writing tools to streamline my workflow. Give me shout and let's make something work.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Digital Developer**

Dieste Inc - June 2015 to Present

Wrote custom Javascript libraries for the development of standard and rich media ads. Currently working on a web application for the rapid development of HTML5 banner advertisements. I develop desktop/mobile ready HTML5 content, using a variety of methods, including hand-written HTML, Javascript, and CSS, as well as Adobe Animate CC. Animate CC projects can also be further customized with per-creative Javascript functions/specialized calls.

## Flash Developer

TM Advertising - February 2013 to June 2015

Flash Developer. Under TM Advertising, I've worked with Discover Network, American Airlines, Japan Airlines, Statoil, Super Pages, and others as well. Projects involved AS2 and AS3 programming/scripting.

#### **Contract Developer**

AMS Pictures - December 2012 to February 2013

Worked on a presentation that included futuristic navigation that was to be displayed on large glass screens via projection. I created the assets in Flash and worked on the graphics, animation, and prototype concepts for the presentation.

## **Independent Game Developer**

espanimation.com - August 2008 to February 2013

Flash animator/developer since 2003. I began scripting/development shortly after and began designing and writing games. I started espanimation.com in 2008 as a site to showcase my animations and games, apart from posting them on gaming sites such as Newgrounds. It's grown since then, and currently garners around 10k visits per day.

#### **EDUCATION**

Art Institute of Pittsburgh 2008 to 2010

#### Film/Cinema

The University of Texas at Arlington - Arlington, TX 2006 to 2008

CSS (3 years), Flash (7 years), HTML (3 years), Javascript (3 years)
LINKS
http://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-posas-80367334
https://github.com/ericposas
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION
Skills: Front-end Web Development, Game Development
Tech: Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, LESS
Learning: PHP
Tools: Brackets (Open Src Editor), Animate CC, Photoshop CC, NetBeans (PHP)
JS Libraries: Greensock, CreateJS, JQuery, Matter.js
Flash games website: http://www.espanimation.com/
GitHub: https://github.com/ericposas

SKILLS